A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Officers' Actions, RG 16 FA474
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Officers' Actions, RG 16
1927-1985
1960-1985
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA474
36.2 Cubic Feet
31 standard record storage boxes. Accession 1: Boxes 1-12. Acession 2: Boxes 1-15, 15A, 16, 17, 18.
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 20 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: grant and fellowship material.
Arrangement
As received.
- Accession 1, 1927-1960; 1
  - Agriculture, Fellowships, 1955-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
  - Agriculture, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 6-12)
  - Agriculture, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 13-18)
  - Agriculture, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19-24)
  - Agriculture, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 25-27)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Fellowships, 1983-1985
  - Agriculture, Grants-in-Aid, New York, 1955-1959
  - Agriculture, Grants-in-Aid, 1960-1965
  - Agriculture, Grants-in-Aid, 1966-1969
  - Agricultural Sciences, Grants-in-Aid, 1983-1985
  - Arts, Grants-in-Aid, 1965-1969
  - Arts, Grants-in-Aid, 1980-1983
  - Arts & Humanities, Grants-in-Aid, 1984-1985
  - Biomedical Research, Fellowships, New York, 1955-1959
  - Biomedical Research, Grants-in-Aid, 1955-1959
  - Conquest of Hunger, Fellowships, 1980-1982
  - Conquest of Hunger, Grants-in-Aid, 1980-1982
  - General, Grants-in-Aid, 1960-1969
  - Humanities and Social Sciences, Fellowships and Scholarships, 1963-1964
  - Medical Sciences Fellowships - New York, 1927-1930 (Box 2)
  - Medical Sciences Fellowships - New York, 1931-1936 (Box 2)
  - Medical Sciences Fellowships - New York, 1937-1950 (Box 2)
  - Humanities Fellowships - New York, 1929-1941 (Box 2)
  - Humanities Fellowships - New York, 1939 (Box 2)
  - Humanities Fellowships - New York, 1953 (Box 2)
  - Humanities Fellowships - New York, 1954-1959 (Box 2)
  - Medical Sciences Fellowships - Paris, 1929-1935 (Box 3)
  - Medical Sciences Fellowships - Paris, 1936-1940 (Box 3)
  - Natural Sciences Fellowships - Paris, 1934-1940 (Box 3)
  - Natural Sciences Fellowships - New York, 1929-1950 (Box 3)
  - Natural Sciences Fellowships - Paris & Peiping, 1929-1933 (Box 3)
  - Medical Education and Public Health (MEPH) Fellowships - New York, 1955-1959 (Box 3)
  - Natural Sciences and Agriculture (NSA) Fellowships - New York, 1951-1953 (Box 3)
  - Social Sciences Fellowships - New York, 1951-1959 (Box 4)
  - Social Sciences Fellowships - Paris, 1929-1931 (Box 4)
  - Social Sciences Fellowships - Paris, 1932-1933 (Box 4)
  - Social Sciences Fellowships - Paris, 1934-1936 (Box 4)
  - Social Sciences Fellowships - Paris, 1937-1940 (Box 4)
  - Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS) Fellowships - New York, 1959 (Box 4)
  - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (LSRM) Fellowships, 1929-1930 (Box 4)
  - International Health Division (IHD) Fellowships, 1927-1929 (Box 5)
  - International Health Division (IHD) Fellowships, 1930-1931 (Box 5)
  - International Health Division (IHD) Fellowships, 1932-1933 (Box 5)
  - International Health Division (IHD) Fellowships, 1934-1935 (Box 5)
  - International Health Division (IHD) Fellowship and Travel Grant Actions, 1936-1938 (Box 5)
  - International Health Division (IHD) Fellowship and Travel Grant Actions, 1939-1941 (Box 5)
  - International Health Division (IHD) Fellowship and Travel Grant Actions, 1942-1945 (Box 6)
  - International Health Division (IHD) Fellowship and Travel Grant Actions, 1946-1948 (Box 6)
  - International Health Division (IHD) Fellowship and Travel Grant Actions, 1949-1950 (Box 6)
  - International Health Division (IHD) Medical Sciences and DMPH Fellowships - New York, 1951-1955 (Box 6)
  - Medical Sciences Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1932-1944 (Box 7)
  - Natural Sciences and Agriculture (NSA) Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1951-1955 (Box 7)
  - Natural Sciences Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1942-1950 (Box 7)
  - Medical Sciences Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1945-1951 (Box 7)
  - Medical Education and Public Health (MEPH) Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1955-1959 (Box 8)
  - Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS) Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1959-1960 (Box 8)
  - Social Sciences Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1935-1944 (Box 8)
  - Social Sciences Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1946-1951 (Box 8)
  - Social Sciences Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1952-1958 (Box 8)
  - Social Sciences Grants-in-Aid, 1959-1960 (Box 8)
  - Humanities Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1930-1939 (Box 9)
  - Humanities Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1940-1944 (Box 9)
  - Humanities Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1945-1950 (Box 9)
  - Humanities Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1951-1955 (Box 9)
  - Humanities Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1956-1960 (Box 9)
  - General Grants-in-Aid, 1950-1960 (Box 9)
  - Medical Sciences Grants-in-Aid: Paris, 1929-1935 (Box 10)
  - Medical Sciences Grants-in-Aid: Paris, 1936-1940 (Box 10)
  - Social Sciences Grants-in-Aid: Paris, 1930-1940 (Box 10)
  - Humanities Grants-in-Aid: Paris, 1939-1940 (Box 10)
  - DMPH Grants-in-Aid, Miscellaneous - New York, 1951-1953 (Box 10)
  - New York, Miscellaneous, 1929-1936 (Box 11)
  - New York, Miscellaneous, 1937-1949 (Box 11)
  - New York, Miscellaneous, 1950-1956 (Box 11)
  - New York, Miscellaneous, 1957-1959 (Box 11)
  - Medical Sciences - British Medical Students, 1941-1945 (Box 11)
  - Allocations - European Rehabilitation, 1948-1952 (Box 11)
  - New York - Hungarian Refugee Program, 1950-1959 (Box 11)
  - Refugee Scholar Program, 1940-1944 (Box 11)
  - International Health Division (IHD) Miscellaneous, 1950-1951 (Box 12)
  - International Health Division (IHD), 1944-1947 (Box 12)
  - International Health Division (IHD), 1948-1950 April (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: New York, 1933-1942 (Box 12)
  - Special Research Aid - New York & Paris, 1933-1940 (Box 12)
  - China, 1933-1941 (Box 12)
  - China, 1942 (Box 12)
- Accession 2, 1929-1985; 1960-1985; 2
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Humanities and Social Sciences (HSS), 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Humanities and Social Sciences (HSS), 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Humanities and Social Sciences (HSS), 1969 (Box 3)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Humanties (HUM), 1960-1962 (Box 3)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Social Sciences (SS), 1960-1962 (Box 3)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS), 1960-1961 (Box 3)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS), 1962-1963 (Box 3)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS), 1964-1965 (Box 3)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS), 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS), 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS), 1960-1961 (Box 5)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS), 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS), 1964-1965 (Box 5)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS), 1966-1968 (Box 5)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Medical and Natural Sciences (MNS), 1969 (Box 5)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Social Sciences (SS), 1960-1962 (Box 5)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities (HUM), 1960-1962 (Box 6)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities and Social Sciences (HSS), 1963-1964 (Box 6)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities and Social Sciences (HSS), 1965-1966 (Box 6)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities and Social Sciences (HSS), 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities and Social Sciences (HSS), 1969 (Box 6)
  - RF Officer's Actions Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 7)
  - RF Officer's Actions Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 7)
  - RF Officer's Actions Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 7)
  - RF Officer's Actions Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 7)
  - RF Officer's Actions Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 7)
  - RF Officer's Actions Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 7)
  - RF Officer's Actions Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 8)
  - RF Officer's Actions Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Agricultural Sciences, 1970 (Box 9)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Agricultural Sciences, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Agricultural Sciences, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Agricultural Sciences, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Agricultural Sciences, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Agricultural Sciences, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Agricultural Sciences, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Agricultural Sciences, 1977 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Agricultural Sciences, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Conquest of Hunger (COH), 1979 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Medical and Natural Sciences, Biomedical Sciences, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Biomedical Sciences, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Biomedical Sciences, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Biomedical Sciences, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Health Sciences, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Health Sciences & HS-RB-F, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & RB - Health Sciences, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Health Sciences, 1977 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Health Sciences, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Health Sciences, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Social Sciences, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Humanities, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Social Sciences, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Humanities, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Natural & Environmental Sciences, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Humanities, 1977 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1977 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Social Sciences, 1977 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Population Division, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Natural & Environmental Sciences, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Humanities, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Social Sciences, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Population Sciences, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Humanities, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Scholarships - Arts & Humanities, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Social Sciences - Humanities & Social Sciences, 1970 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Social Sciences, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Social Sciences, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Arts and Humanities, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Social Sciences, 1973 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Arts and Humanities, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Humanities, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships - Education for Development, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Fellowships & Scholarships - Social Sciences, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Medical and Natural Science, Biomedical Sciences, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Biomedical Sciences, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Biomedical Sciences, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Biomedical Sciences, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Agricultural Sciences, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Agricultural Sciences, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Agricultural Sciences, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Agricultural Sciences, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Agricultural Sciences, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Agricultural Sciences, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Agricultural Sciences, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Agricultural Sciences, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Agricultural Sciences, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Arts, 1974 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Arts, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Arts, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Arts, 1977 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Arts, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Arts, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Arts and Humanities, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Arts & Humanities, 1971 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Arts and Humanities, 1972 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Arts and Humanities, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Conquest of Hunger, 1979 (Box 11)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Equal Opportunity, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Education for Development, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Inter-Departmental (1971) (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Interdisciplinary, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Interdisciplinary, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Interdisciplinary, 1974 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Interdisciplinary, 1975 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Interdisciplinary, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Interdisciplinary, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Interdisciplinary, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: International Relations, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: International Relations, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: International Relations, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: International Relations, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities and Social Sciences, 1970 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities, 1974 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities, 1975; No label (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Inter-Program, 1970 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Social Sciences, 1971 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Social Sciences, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Social Sciences, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Social Sciences, 1974 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Social Sciences, 1975 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Social Sciences, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Social Sciences, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Social Sciences, 1978 (Box 12)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1972 (Box 13)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1973 (Box 13)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1976 (Box 13)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1977 (Box 13)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Natural and Environmental Sciences, 1978 (Box 13)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Population Division, 1978 (Box 13)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Population Division, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Special Interests & Explorations (SIE), 1979 (Box 13)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Quality of the Environment, 1979 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1972 January-June (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1972 July-December (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1973 January-June; loose label. (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. II, and Donations of Equipment, 1973 July-December (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1974 January-June (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1974 July-December (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donations of Equipment, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1975 January-June (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1975 July-December (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1976 January-May (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1976 June-December (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donation of Equipment, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1977 January-June (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1977 July-December (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donations of Equipment, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1978 January-May (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1978 June-December (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. III, "E" Numers and Donation of Equipment, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donations of Equipment, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1979 January-June (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1979 July-December (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donation of Equipment, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Fellowships - Education for Development, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Education for Development, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Education for Development, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Education for Development, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Education for Development, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Special Postdoctoral Fellowships, 1977-1982 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Health Sciences, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Health Sciences, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Health Sciences, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Health Sciences, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Health Sciences, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Population Sciences, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Population Sciences, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Population Sciences, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Population Sciences, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Fellowships - Population Sciences, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. III, "E" Numbers and Donations of Equipment, 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1980 July-December (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1982 (Box 15A)
  - Fellowships - Humanities, 1982 (Box 15A)
  - Fellowships - Humanities, 1983 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Education for Development, 1982 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Education for Development, 1984 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Education for Development, 1985 (Box 15A)
  - Fellowships - Population Sciences, 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Education for Development, 1981 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1981 (Box 15A)
  - Fellowships - Humanities, 1981 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Population Sciences, 1981 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Special Interests & Explorations (SIE), 1981 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Special Interests & Explorations (SIE), 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Education for Development, 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Fellowships - Education for Development, 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Fellowships - Health Sciences, 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Fellowships - Humanities, 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Equal Opportunity, 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities, 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: International Relations, 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Population Sciences, 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1980 (Box 15A)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1980 January-June (Box 15A)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Population Sciences (PS), 1983 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Population Sciences (PS), 1982 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Special Interests & Explorations (SIE), 1985 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Special Interests & Explorations (SIE), 1984 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Special Interests & Explorations (SIE), 1983 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Special Interests & Explorations (SIE), 1982 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Equal Opportunity (EO), 1981 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Equal Opportunity (EO), 1982 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Equal Opportunity (EO), 1983 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Equal Opportunity (EO), 1984 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Equal Opportunity (EO), 1985 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Health Sciences, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities, 1981 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Humanities, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Inter-Program, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Inter-Program, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Inter-Program, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: International Relations, 1981 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: International Relations, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: International Relations, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: International Relations, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: International Relations, 1985 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Population Sciences (PS), 1984 (Box 16)
  - Grants-in-Aid: Population Sciences (PS), 1985 (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1981 January-May (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. II, 1981 June-December (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1982 January-December (Box 17)
  - Officers' Actions "E" Numbers and Donation Equipment, Vol. II, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1983 January-December (Box 17)
  - Officers' Actions "E" Numbers and Donation of Equipment, Vol. II, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1984 January-December (Box 17)
  - Officers' Actions "E" Numbers and Donation of Equipment, Vol. II, 1984 (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous Vol. I, 1985 January-December (Box 17)
  - Officers' Actions "E" Numbers; Donation of Equipment; Special Postdoctoral Fellowships, Vol. II, 1985 (Box 17)
  - Fellowship Regulations, 1929-1948 (Box 18)
  - Fellowship - Miscellaneous, 1950s (Box 18)
  - Fellowship Conference Minutes, 1950-1959 (Box 18)
  - Fellowship Conference Minutes, 1960-1965 (Box 18)
  - Fellowship Conference Minutes - Extracts - A-P, 1945-1965 (Box 18)
  - Fellowship Conference Minutes - Extracts - Q-Z, 1945-1965 (Box 18)
  - Fellowship Conference Minutes, 1945-1967 (Box 18)
  - Fellowship Memoranda, 1958-1967 (Box 18)
  - Fellowship Conferences - Index to Minutes - Index Cards, 1945-1967 (Box 18)
  - Committee on Scholars/Fellows, 1973-1974 (Box 18)